A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.37 (A2012) FA472
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2012.073: Rockefeller Foundation records, grants management office, 1992, 1996, 1998-2008; bulk; AC 2012:073; 17.55 Cubic Feet 13 standard record storage boxes, 1 letter document box, and 1 oversize box
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 6.57 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - Resident (Hoxie, Frederick E.), 2004-2006 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Hyden, Goran), 2004-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Johnson, Denis), 2004-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Jones, Kellie E.), 2004-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Joshi, Sushma), 2004-2006 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Kaplan, George A.), 2004-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Kapur, Malavika), 2004-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Kartun-Blum, Ruth), 2002-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Kim, Young Jak) (Co-Resident: Otake, Hideo), 2004-2006 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (King, Patricia A.), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (King, Patricia A.), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Kitzke, Jerome), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Koczanowicz, Leszek), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Kopelson, Kevin Richard), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Kuharic, Katharine M.), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Lazarovici, Cornelia-Magda)(Co-Resident: Lazarovici, Gheorghe C.), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Lazreg, Marnia), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Leron, Uri), 2003-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Levinson, Sanford), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Lewin, Hugh Framcis), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Lio, Laura B. Martorelli), 2003-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Little Wyman, Deborah W.), 2004-2006 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (MacDonald, Michael Patrick), 2004-2006 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Mann, James H.), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (May, Elaine Tyler), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (McGarrell, James), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (McGrath, John Joseph), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (McNair, Wesley C.), 2004-2006 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Moi, Toril), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Moore, Honor), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Mulholland, Dulcie A.), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Nathanson, Constance A.), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Neuhouser, Frederick), 2004-2005 (Box R3968)
    - Resident (Oates, Ronald Kim), 2004-2008 (Box R3968)
      Restricted - Fellowship Files - Open in 2029
    - Resident (Oliver, Melvin L.)(Co-Resident: Shapiro, Thomas M.), 2004-2006 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Pangalangan, Raul C.), 2004-2006 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Pen, Polly), 2004-2005 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Philip, M. Nourbese), 2005-2006 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Rousseve, David John), 2004-2005 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Ruiz, Benardo), 2004-2005 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Sazonova, Lidia Ivanovna), 2004-2005 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Scheffer, John R.), 2004-2006 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Sharma, Yuyutsu Ram Dass), 2004-2005 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Shaw, Jane Alison), 2004-2006 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Simons-Morton, Bruce Gordon), 2004-2005 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Singleton, Alvin E.), 2004-2005 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Smith, Carl S.), 2005 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Spiro, Ellen Rae), 2005-2006 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Stearns, Stephen Curtis), 2004-2005 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Steinnberg, David I.), 2004-2006 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Strauss, Peter L.), 2004-2006 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Teixeira Coelho, Jose), 2003-2005 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Tejada-Flores, Rick), 2005-2006 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Thomson, Jennifer Ann), 2004-2005 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Tileston, Jackie), 2004-2005 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Umar, Nasaruddin), 2003-2005 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Westphal, Heiner), 2004-2005 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Wilkins, Roger W.), 2004-2005 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Wright, Stuart A.), 2004-2009 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Yaroshinskaya, Alla Aleksandra), 2004-2005 (Box R3969)
    - Resident (Yeazell, Ruth Bernard), 2005-2007 (Box R3969)
      Restricted - Fellowship Files - Open in 2028
    - Resident (Yovel, Yirmiyahu), 2004-2005 (Box R3969)
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), 8.35 Cubic Feet 6 record storage boxes, 1 letter document box, and 1 oversize box
    - Princeton University - Cultural Conflict in Contemporary U.S. (1,+ 1 Supplemental Folder) - 2000 CC 023, 2000-2004 (Box R3960)
    - Performing Arts Journal - Support for Publications - 200 CC 032, 2000-2004 (Box R3960)
    - Atlatl - Exhibition, "Who Stole the Tee-Pee" - 2000 CC 036, 1999-2000 (Box R3961)
    - Brown Dance Co. - Thirtieth Anniversary Activities - 2000 CC 041, 2000-2004 (Box R3961)
    - House Foundation for the Arts - Site Specific Work, "American Archeology #3" - 2000 CC 056, 2000-2003 (Box R3961)
    - Walker Art Center - "The End of Cinematics" - 2000 CC 080, 2000-2004 (Box R3961)
    - The End of the Cinematics - Director Mikel Rouse, 2012:073:002 (Box R3961)
    - African Publishers' Network - Promote African Publishing (5+ 2 Suppl.) - 2000 CC 099, 1992-2005 (Box R3961, Box R3962)
    - African Publishers' Network - Promote African Publishing (5+ 1 Suppl.) - 2000 CC 099, 1992-2005 (Box R3961, Box R3962)
    - Photo Archive Group - Danang Phase of "The American War Project" - 2000 CC 102, 1998-2004 (Box R3962)
    - 2000 CC 102, 2012:073:003 (Box SF2)
    - Another Vietnam: Pictures of the War from the Other Side [Published Materials], 2012:073:026 (Box R3962)
    - New York University - Hemispheric Institute's "Encuentros" Seminars - 2000 CC 128, 2000-2004 (Box R3962)
    - Urban Institute - Study of Support Mechanisms for U.S. Artists - 2000 CC 131, 2000-2003 (Box R3962)
    - Center for Arts and Culture - General Programming - 2000 CC 151, 1998-2004 (Box R3962)
    - The Politics of Culture; Policy Perspectives for Individuals, Institutions, and Communities, 2012:073:016 (Box R3962)
    - Crossroads; Art and Religion in American Life, 2012:073:017 (Box R3962)
    - Access and the Cultural Infrastructure; Center for Arts and Culture, 2012:073:020 (Box R3962)
    - Globalization and Cultural Diplomacy; Center for Arts and Culture, 2012:073:021 (Box R3962)
    - Creativity, Culture, Education and the Workforce (Published Material), 2012:073:022 (Box R3962)
    - National Investments in the Arts, 2012:073:023 (Box R3962)
    - Dartmouth College - Exhibition, "Jose Clemente Orozco in the United States, 1927-1934" - 2000 CC 152, 2000-2004 (Box R3963)
    - Jose Clemente Orozco In the United States, 1927-1934, Hood Museum of Art, 2012:073:004 (Box SF1)
    - Jose Clemente Orozco in the United States, 1927-1934, 2012:073:019 (Box R3963)
    - Columbia University - Conference on Arts and the First Amendment, 2001 CC 029, 2000-2003 (Box R3963)
    - The New Gate Keepers: Emerging Challenges to Free Expression in the Arts, 2012:073:024 (Box R3963)
    - University of Wisconsin - "Caribbean Artist Series" (Milwaukee) - 2001 CC 033, 2000-2005 (Box R3963)
    - Institute of Visual Art - 2011 CC 033, 2012:073:005 (Box SF1)
    - Fund For Independent Publishing - Book and Tape Set, "Remembering Jim Crow" - 2001 CC 042, 2000-2004 (Box R3963)
    - Remembering Jim Crow; African Americans tell About Life in the Segregated South, 2012:073:018 (Box R3963)
    - Mexico-North Research Network - Preserving/Renewing Raramuri Cultural Heritage Through the Textile Arts - 2001 CC 046, 2000-2003 (Box R3963)
    - National Council of La Raza - National Association of Latino Independent Producers Multi-Year Support - 2001 CC 052, 2001-2002 (Box R3963)
    - Association for Cultural Equity - Preservation of Alan Lomax Folklore Archives - 2001 CC 053, 1999-2003 (Box R3963)
    - Bang on a Can - E Festival - 2001 CC 061, 2001-2002 (Box R3963)
    - University of Chicago - Conference on "Contingent Valuation of Culture", 2001-2003 (Box R3963)
    - Asia Society - Exhibition Series, "Conversations with Tradition" - 2001 CC 065, 2000-2004 (Box R3963)
    - University of California - "The Contemporary Kastina" (Los Angeles) - 2001 CC 076, 2000-2004 (Box R3963)
    - Katsina: Commodified and Appropriated Images of Hopi Supernaturals, 2012:073:025 (Box R3963)
    - Fund for Folk Culture - Capacity Building in Field of Folk and Traditional Culture - 2001 CC 105, 2001-2004 (Box R3963)
    - United States Conference of Religions for Peace - Meetings on Religious Responses to Interfaith Conflicts, 2001 CC 107, 2001-2004 (Box R3964)
    - Commemoration and Commitment; The United States Conference of Religions for Peace, 2012:073:014 (Box R3964)
    - University of New Mexico - Creating an Arts Environment in High Performance Computing - 2001 CC 114, 2001-2003 (Box R3964)
    - ATC Rockefeller NEA, Artists-in-Residence, Workshop Discussion, 2012:073:006 (Box R3964)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - New York University - Gender and Cultural Citizenship Project - 2001 CC 117, 2000-2004 (Box R3964)
    - Acontemporary Theatre - "John School" - 2001 CC 120, 2001-2005 (Box R3964)
    - Carpetbag Theatre - "Spoken Word Opera" - 2001 CC 125, 2001-2003 (Box R3964)
    - The Carpetbag Theatre, Inc's - American Sankofa Remember 33 Years of Music, Theatre and People, 2012:073:007 (Box R3964)
    - SW Opera: A Spoken Word Opera, 2012:073:008 (Box R3964)
      Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - Jane Comfort and Co. - Dance-Theatre piece, "Persephone" - 2001 CC 153, 2001-2003 (Box R3964)
    - Walker Art Center - Virtual Arts Network (Van) Planning Grant - 2001 CC 168, 2000-2003 (Box R3964)
    - University of the Republic, Uruguay - Resident Fellowships on Cultural Policies and Civil Society - 2001 CC 169, 1996-2003 (Box R3964)
    - City University of New York - New Immigrant Women's Oral History Project - 2001 CC 174, 2001-2003 (Box R3964)
    - Crossing the Boulevard: Strangers, Neighbors, Aliens in a New America - 2001 cc 199 (A12) (Box R3970)
    - GEI Arts presents Urban Bush Women in "Hair Stories" - Triangle Theater @ LIU - 2001 cc 183 (Box R3970)
    - Beter Neighborhoods Same Neighbors, 6.10.3 - 2001 cc 194 (A12) (Box R3970)
    - Crossing the Boulevard; radio segments produced by WNYC's The Next Big Thing -1002 cc 188 (A12) (Box R3970)
  - African Regional (AR), 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - African Aids Research Network (Senegal) - Capacity Building and Fundraising Strategies Workshop - 2002 AR 055, 2002-2005 (Box R3960)
    - Forum for African Women Educationalists, Uganda Chapter Management of Sexual Maturation in Primary Schools - 2002 AR 057, 2002-2004 (Box R3960)
    - Boost Fellowship Foundation - Partnership for Africa Renewal - 2002 AR 062, 2000-2004 (Box R3960)
    - Ministry of Health, Ghana - Meeting on Demographic Surveillance System - 2003 AR 008, 2003-2004 (Box R3960)
    - International Livestock Research Institute (Kenya) - Database on Poverty for East Africa - 2003 AR 010, 2000-2004 (Box R3960)
    - Geographic Dimensions of Well-Being in Kenya - Where are the Poor?, 2012:073:001 (Box R3960)
    - Geographic Dimensions of Well-Being in Kenya - where are the poor? From Districts to Locations, Volume 1, 2012:073:028 (Box R3960)
    - University of Natal (South Africa) - International Biometrics Society Conference - 2003 AR 012, 2003-2008 (Box R3960)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - The Status of Women, Annoted Bibliography. UNESCO - RF 99055 (A12) (Box R3953)
  - Assets and Capacities (AC), 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - AfriAfya - African Network of Health Knowledge Management and Communication - Issue Nov. October 2003 - 2002 AC 117 (A12) (Box R3956)
- AC.2012.077: Rockefeller Foundation records, grants, 1994-2006; AC_2012_077; 9.58 Cubic Feet 7 standard record storage boxes and 1 letter document box
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), 6.95 Cubic Feet 5 letter document boxes and 1 letter document box
    - Columbia University - BC Conference: New Faces Colloquium on Religion, Human Rights and Societal Reconstruction in a Pluralist World - 2001 CC 176, 2001-2003 (Box R3970)
    - L.A. Freewave - "The Big Box: Arts and the Mass Media" - 2001 CC 180, 2001-2003 (Box R3970)
    - 651 Arts - "Hairstories: - 2001 CC 183, 2001-2003 (Box R3970)
    - Alutiiq Heritage Foundation - Traditional Woodcarving Workshops - 2001 CC 184, 2001-2004 (Box R3970)
    - PACT Report YZ, Alutiiq Museum, Kodiak, AK, 2012:077:001 (Box R3970)
      Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, of if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
    - Appalshop - Media Arts project, "From the Holler to the Hood..." - 2001 CC 185, 2001-2004 (Box R3970)
    - Conference: Promises and Pitfalls of International Courts - 120, 2002-2004 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Public Values, System Design and the Public Domain - 120, 2001-2003 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Redux Metabolism in Malaria: From Genes to Drugs - 120, 2001-2003 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Social Consequenes of Rumor and Legend - 120, 2001-2003 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Social Movements and Contentious Politics in a Democratizing World - 120, 2001-2003 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Trans/cultural Translators: Mediating Race, Indigeneity, Ethnicity in Four Nations - 120, 2002-2003 (Box R3974)
    - Amory Center for the Arts - "Manos de Esperanza/Hands of Hope" - 2001 CC 186, 2001-2003 (Box R3970)
    - Elders Share the Arts - Media Project on New Immigrants in Queens, New York - 2001 CC 188, 2000-2005 (Box R3970)
    - Philadelphia Mural Arts Advocates - Youth Arts Education Program - 2001 CC 191, 2001-2003 (Box R3970)
    - Strategic Actions for a Just Economy - Project, "We Shall Not Be Moved" - 2001 CC 194, 2001-2004 (Box R3970)
    - White Earth Reservation - "Honoring the Seven Fires..." - 2001 CC 196, 2001-2004 (Box R3970)
    - RIWAQ: Centre for Architectural Conservation (Israel) - National Register of Palestinian Sites and Buildings - 2001 CC 210, 1994-2003 (Box R3971)
    - The Palestinian Village home, Suad Amiry and Vera Tamari [ISBN: 0-7141-1599-1] 2001 cc 210 (A2012), 2012:077:002 (Box R3971)
    - Traditional Floor Tiles in Palestine, Saud Amiry and Lena Sobeyh, 2001 cc 210 (A2012), 2012:077:003 (Box R3971)
    - International African Institute (England) - Bellagio Publishing Network Meetings - 2001 CC 217, 2001-2004 (Box R3971)
    - New York University - "New Media and Cultural Activism" Project - 2001 CC 218, 2001-2003 (Box R3971)
    - University of California - Low-Cost Production Guide for Makers of Documentaries (Berkeley) - 2001 CC 219, 2001-2004 (Box R3971)
    - American Museum of the Moving Image - "Digital Arts Project Room" - 2001 CC 220, 2001-2003 (Box R3971)
    - Graduate School and University Center, City University of New York - "Streaming Culture", 2001-2004 (Box R3971)
    - African Books Collective, Ltd. - Compile and Distribute Publications, 1988-2002 (Box R3971, Box R3972)
    - African Books Collective, Ltd. - Compile and Distribute Publications - 2001 CC 231, 1988-2002 (Box R3971, Box R3972)
    - The African Writers' Handbook, Edited by James Gibbs andJack Mapanje. 2001 cc 231 (A12) [ISBN: 0-9521269-6-61], 2012:077:025 (Box R3972)
    - African Books Collective, Ltd. - Compile and Distribute Publications - 2001 CC 231 (Box R3972)
    - Lehman College Art Gallery - Exhibition, "Taino Treasures: The Legacy of Dr. Ricardo Alegria" - 2002 CC 001, 2000-2003 (Box R3972)
    - Taino/Alegria Symposium, March 20, 2003 - 2002 cc 001 (A2012), 2012:077:005 (Box R3972)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please consult a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - Cuentos Foundation - "Ritmo de Fuego/Rhythm of Fire" - 2002 CC 004, 2000-2003 (Box R3972)
    - Cuentos, 2012:077:004 (Box SF1)
    - Old Sturbridge Vilage - Exhibition, "The Enduring People: Native American Life in Central New England" - 2002 CC 008, 2001-2003 (Box R3972)
    - Electronic Literature Organization - Electronic Literature Directory - 2002 CC 011, 2001-2003 (Box R3975)
    - Bellevue Art Museum - Exhibition, "Alfredo Arreguin: Patterns of Dreams and Nature" - 2001 CC 012, 2000-2002 (Box R3975)
    - Bellevue Art Museum 2002 cc 012 (A2012), 2012:077:008 (Box SF1)
    - Alfredo Arreguin, Patterns of Dreams and Nature - Sisenos Suenos and Naturaleza, Lauro Flores. 2002 ss 012 (A2012) [ISBN: 0-295-98178-4], 2012:077:009 (Box R3975)
    - De Marinis, Paul - Multi-Media Installation on How Technologies Grow Out of Dreams - 2002 CC 013, 2002-2004 (Box R3975)
    - Paul DeMarinis, Firebirds, 2002 cc 013 (A2012), 2012:077:007 (Box R3975)
    - Hoberman, Perry - Multi-Media Installation, "Table of Contents" - 2002 CC 014, 2002-2005 (Box R3975)
    - Sandin, Daniel J. - Virtual Reality Installaiton, "Looking for Water 2" - 2002 CC 016, 2002-2004 (Box R3975)
    - Lopez-Shaw, Gabriel - "Indigenous Movement: Gwichiin" - 2002 CC 017, 2002-2005 (Box R3975)
    - Aguilar, Mariano Estrada - "Hacia El Horizonte (Toward the Horizon)" - 2002 CC 019, 2002-2003 (Box R3975)
    - Mariano Estrada, Mujer Indigena (La video Olivdada) 2002 cc 109 (A2012), 2012:077:010 (Box R3975)
    - Rojas, Carlos Efrain Perez - Documentary on Environmental Damage Caused by Deforestation in Southern Mexico - 2002 CC 020, 2002-2006 (Box R3975)
    - Cobo, Ernestina Grade Quintanilla - "Bits de Memoria (Bits of Memory)" - 2002 CC 021, 2002-2004 (Box R3975)
    - Asia Society - "Through Afghan Eyes" Exhibition and Related Programs - 2002 CC 022, 2001-2004 (Box R3975)
    - Brewer, Craig - "Hustle and Flow" - 2002 CC 027, 2002-2005 (Box R3975)
    - Hustle and Flow, 2002 cc 027 (A2012), 2012:077:011 (Box R3975)
    - Brown, Bill - Experimental Documentary, "This Side of the Border" - 2002 CC 028, 2002-2004 (Box R3975)
    - Choy, Curtis - Documentary About Author Frank Chin - 2002 CC 029, 2002-2004 (Box R3975)
    - Dunn, Laura - Documentary, "Mayim" - 2002 CC 030, 2002-2004 (Box R3975)
    - Finley, Jeanne C. and Muse, John - "Age of Consent" - 2002 CC 031, 2002-2004 (Box R3975)
    - Hoffmann, Deborah and Reis, Francis - Documentary, "The Women's Voices Project" - 2002 CC 033, 2002-2004 (Box R3975)
    - Mullington, Andrew - Narrative Film, "Zumbi's Dream" - 2002 CC 034, 2002-2004 (Box R3975)
    - Nilsson, Rob - "9 @ Night Films" - 2002 CC 035, 2002-2004 (Box R3975)
    - Osawa, Sandi Sunrising - Documentary on Maria Tallchief - 2002 CC 036, 2002-2004 (Box R3975)
    - Rowley, Richard G. - Video Documentary, "We Were Born in the Night" - 2002 CC 037, 2002-2004 (Box R3975)
    - Richard Rowley, The Forth World War 2002 cc 037 (A2012), 2012:077:037 (Box R3975)
    - Sinnokrot, Nida - "Grounds" - 2002 CC 038, 2002-2004 (Box R3975)
    - Takesue, KIMI - "Skipping Stones", 2002-2004 (Box R3975)
    - New School University - Conference, "Blue 02: Power at Play in Digital Art and Culture" - 2002 CC 040, 2001-2003 (Box R3975)
    - Projects and Prototypes/Open Play 2002 cc 040 (A2012), 2012:077:013 (Box R3975)
    - Projects and Prototypes/The Network Moment 2002 cc 040 (A2012), 2012:077:014 (Box R3975)
    - Framing, 2002 cc 040 s (A2012), 2012:077:015 (Box R3975)
    - Code and Culture 2002 cc 040 s (A2012), 2012:077:016 (Box R3975)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for futher instruction.
    - Scenario Planning Presentations 2002 cc 040 s (A2012), 2012:077:017 (Box R3975)
      Access currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC Archivist for further instruction.
    - "Truisms and Consequences" 2002 cc 040 s (A2012), 2012:077:018 (Box R3975)
    - IP 2002 cc 040 s (A2012), 2012:077:019 (Box R3975)
    - Diverse Works Art Space - Exhibition, "William Pope L.: eRacism" - 2002 CC 042, 2001-2004 (Box R3975)
    - Institute of Contemporary Art, William Pope L. - 2002 cc-042 (A2012), 1997; 2012:077:020 (Box SF1)
    - William Pope L: eRacism, DiverseWorks Artspace, 2002 cc 042 (A2012), 2012:077:021 (Box R3975)
    - William Pope.L The Friendliest Black Artist in America 2002 cc 042 (A2012) [ISBN: 0-262002533-7], 2012:077:022 (Box R3975)
    - University of Southern California - Exhibition and Publication, "Mixed Feelings: Art and Culture in a Postborder Metropolis" - 2002 CC 043, 2001-2003 (Box R3975)
    - Mixed Feelings, USC Fisher Gallery, 2002 cc 043 (A2012), 2012:077:024 (Box R3975)
    - Mixed Feelings, San Diego/Tijuana, 2002 cc 043 (A2012), 2012:077:023 (Box R3975)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - "Ta'ziyeh" and other Middle Eastern Productions at 2002 Festival - 2002 CC 044, 2001-2003 (Box R3975)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - Conference: Achieving Diversity in Tertiary and Higher Education: Challenges and Prospects, 2001-2004 (Box R3973)
    - Conference: Capacity Building, Lessons and Future Directions, 2002-2006 (Box R3973)
    - Conference: Caribbean in New York and Paris, 2002-2004 (Box R3973)
    - Conference: Conservation and Sustainable Management of Sea Turtles in the Pacific Ocean, 2002-2006 (Box R3973)
    - Conference: Current Status of Research and Opportunities for Collaboration with Industry, 2003 (Box R3973)
    - Conference: Developing a New Strategic Plan for IPFF, 2002-2003 (Box R3973)
    - Conference: Ethical Globalization Initiative Human Rights Building Group, 2002-2004 (Box R3973)
    - Conference: Finding Out What Works: Evaluating Complex Community Change Initiatives in the US and the UK, 2002-2004 (Box R3973)
    - Conference: From Pilot Projects to Policies and Programs: Strategies for Scaling Up Innovations in health Service Delivery, 2002-2003 (Box R3973)
    - Conference: Global Perspectives on Youth Conflict, 2002-2004 (Box R3973)
    - Conference: Global Value Chains, 2002-2003 (Box R3973)
    - Conference: Human Resources in Health Series: Coordinating Group, 2003-2004 (Box R3973)
    - Conference: Human Resources in Health Series: Explorations in Global Health History, 2003 (Box R3973)
    - Conference: Human Resources in Health Series: History of Global Public Health, 2002-2003 (Box R3973)
    - Conference: Influence of Cooperative Bacteria on Animal Host Biology, 2002-2006 (Box R3973)
    - Conference: Internal Conflict in GMO Regulation, 2002-2004 (Box R3973)
    - Conference: Internal PEN Strategic Planning and Capacity Building Meeting, 2002-2004 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: International Rural Strategies Alliance, 2002-2004 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Justice in the Balance: Rebuilding Communities in the Aftermath of Genocide and Ethnic Cleansing in Rwanda and the Former Yugoslavia, 2002-2003 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Knowledge into Action: Improving Equity in Child Health, 2002-2005 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Latin America and Chicano/a Art Criticism since the 1940s: Between Modernity and Globalization, 2002-2004 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Muslim Women Challenge Fundamentalism: Building Bridges between Southeast Asia and West Asia, 2003-2004 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Narrative, Pain and Suffering, 2002-2004 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Partnership on Strengthening Higher Education in Africa, 2002-2003 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Planning Session for New Tactics in Human Rights, 2002-2005 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Promises and Pitfalls of Inernational Courts, 2002-2004 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Public Values, System Design and the Public Domain, 2001-2003 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Redox Metabolism in Malaria: From Genes to Drugs, 2001-2003 (Box R3974)